National Council for the Traditional Arts (NCTA) collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Performer and Genre Lists
  - Genres
New Orleans Street Percussion
New York-style salsa
Newfoundland
Newfoundland songs, stories and tunes
Nipmuc flute player and maker
North Indian Kathak dancer
Northumbrian Pipes
Norwegian Fiddle
Norwegian Folk Music
Norwegian Rosemaler
Norwegian woodcarving
Ojibwe basketmakers & storytellers
Okinawan-American Musician
Old Time - Missouri Fiddle
Old Time Maine Dance Hall Orchestra
Old-Time
Old-Time - Appalachian Guitarist
Old-time and Irish music/dance
Old-Time Banjo
Old-Time Country Singing
Old-Time Fiddle
old-time fiddling
old-time music
Old-time Square and Contra Dance
Old-time String Band
old-time, bluegrass, country rock
Organ
Oud maker
Ozark fiddle
Ozark Tall Tales
pan pipes
Papago Music
Paraguay - Folk Music
Paraguayan Harp & Vocal Music
Passamaquoddy-basket weaver
Penitentes of New Mexico
Persian
Persian Santur Player
Philippino Traditional Dance
Photo Documentarian, Author & Exhibit Curator
Piano
Piano - Barrelhouse
Piano various styles
Piano-Cape Breton
Piano-Gospel
Piedmont blues guitar & harmonica
Piedmont Old Time Banjo
Play Party Games
Polish
Polish Mountain Music and Dance
Polish Polka
Polish-American
Polka
Polka - Dutch Hop style
Polka - East Coast Style
Polka - German
Polka - Polish
Polka - Slovenian
Polka-Texas-Polish
Portuguese - Azorean
Portuguese Fado Music
Portuguese-American
Pottery - Santa Clara pueblo
Presenter
Puerto Rican
Puerto Rican Bomba
Puerto Rican Bomba y Plena
Puerto Rico - Jibaro
Puerto Rico - Plena
Punch and Judy, The Ancient Art of
Puppetry for Kids
pure
Quebeçois
Québécois music
Québécois Music & Dance
Quebecois Music, Song and Dance
R & B and Doo-Wop
Raga Music from North and South India
Ragtime
Recitation
Record producer and label founder
Reggae
Rhythm and Blues
Rio Grande Weaver
Rock
Rock n Roll
Rockabilly
Rodeo poetry
Romanian
Rug Hooking
Russian
Russian & Ukrainian
Russian Domra & Bayan
Sacred Harp Singing
Sacred Steel Guitar
Salsa
Salsa/Merengue Dance Music
Santero
Santero (carver & painter of sacred figures)
Scandinavian Dance
Scottish
Scottish and Cape Breton Gaelic
Scottish Dance
Scottish pipe & drum band
Scottish Pipe Band
Scottish Songs and Ballads
Sea Chanteys
Sea Islands - African-American
Senegalese - drum maker
Senegalese Griot and Kora
Sephardic Singer
Shape Note Singing
Sicilian
Sicilian - Traditional Music
Silly Humor for Kids
Singer/Songwriter
Skiffle
Skokomish tradition bearer, carver, basket maker
Slavic Music And Dance
Slavic Tamburitzen
Slovenian Polkas
Songster - African American
Soul
Soul and R & B
South African mbaqanga
South Indian Bharata Natyam classical dance
South Indian Veena
Southeast Asia-Hmong
Soviet Union
Soviet Union - Georgian
Soviet Union - Nerekhtski Horn Playing
Soviet Union - Tuvan
Soviet Union - Ukraine
Spanish religious chants
Spiritual
Split ash basketmaker - New Hampshire
Spoken word
Spoons
Square Dance
Square Dance Caller
Stage Sounds
Steel Drum
Stepping
Stone Carver & Calligrapher
Storyteller
Storytellers - Adirondack
Storytellers - African-American
Storytellers - Jack Tales
Storytellers - Jewish
Storytellers - Maine
Storytellers - Vermont
Storyteller-Smith Island (Chesapeake Bay)
Storytelling
Storytelling - New England Downeast
Straw oppliqué artist
String & Instruction
String Band
String Band/Blues
Swedish-American
Swedish-American Fiddle
Swing -Texas
Tabetan Dance
Taiko drummer and dojo founder
Talk
Tamburitzan
Tamburitzan instrument maker
Tejano
Tejano Conjunto Music
Test Tones from Original Source
Texas Country Blues And Ballads
Texas Fiddling
Texas-Czech Polka
Texas-Mexican Conjunto Music
Tibetan Folk Songs
Tibetan Sacred Music
Tibetan Sacred Music & Dance
Tibetan sand mandala painter
Tin and Embroidery - Hispanic-American
Tlingit Chilkat Blanket Weaver
Tole Painting
Tolowa traditional bearer
Traditional Arabic Music
Traditional British Songs
Trinidadian Calypso
Trinidadian Steelpan
Tsimashian Dance
Tuku Music from Zimbabwe
U.S. - Popular Music
U.S. - Traditional Mountain Music
Ugandan Afro-Pop
Ugandan Folk/Jazz
Ukrainian
Ukrainian-American Pysanky
United House Of Prayer Gospel Brass
United House Of Prayer Gospel Shout
Unknown
Urban Country
Various Accordion Styles
Various Banjo Styles
Various Dance Styles
Various Fiddle Styles
Various French Musical Styles
Various Guitar Styles
Various Musical Styles
Various Singing Styles
Various Styles - Hand Drumming
Various Styles - wind instruments
Various vocal styles
Various-percussion
Various-Stringed Instruments
Veracruz Trio Jarocho
Vietnamese - Court and Chamber Music
Vietnamese - Traditional
Virgin Islands Quadrille & Scratch Music
Waila - Native American dance music
Walk-In Music
Wasco Sally Bag Weaver
West African Drumming
Western
Western Music
Western Saddlemaker
Western Swing
Whistling
Wildfowl decoy carver
Woodcarver
Working Arts
Workshop
Yankee Dulcimer and Fiddle
Yankee Fiddle
Yaqui Pascola Music of Arizona
Yiddish - Actor
Yiddish - Actress
Yiddish Folksongs
Yiddish Singer, Poet, Songwriter
Yugoslavian dance
Zydeco